global-exam.com 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy

Privacy and security are of utmost importance to GlobalExam and we strive to ensure that our technical and organisational measures in place respect your data protection rights.

This Privacy Policy describes how we manage, process and store personal data submitted in the context of providing our services. “ ** _Personal data_** ” refers to any information relating to an identifiable individual or his or her personal identity.

## Consent

In subscribing to our services or filling in a contact form on our website (global-exam.com) you agree and accept that we may gather, process, store and/or use the personal data submitted in accordance with the rules set forth below.

By giving your consent to us, you also retain the right to have your personal data rectified, to be forgotten and/or to be erased.

## Personal Data Collected

### Identity and contact details of the data processor

Personal data is collected on our website by GlobalExam SAS, a company registered under the laws of France under number 795 246 396 with the Nanterre Trade & Companies Register, and having its registered office at 53 rue Fénelon 92120 Montrouge, France.

### Data Protection Authority Declarations

Declarations on the automated processing of data have been registered with the French data protection authority (CNIL) under number 1701688 v 0.

You retain the right to lodge any complaints on data protection with this supervisory authority.

### Data collected on the site

When you use our platform and/or when you register, we collect and process your personal data such as your first name when you create an account.

We also ask you to give us your email so we can use this data to create an account, confirm this account, send informational and transactional emails as well as our newsletter.

By using our services, the following data is collected and managed: log-on data and browsing data where you authorise it, order history, complaints, incidents, information on subscriptions and messages on our site. Some data is collected automatically by reason of your activity on the site (see paragraph on cookies below).

When you register on the platform, you can register through Facebook, Google Account or Linkedin. If you connect to our services through this social media platforms, GlobalExam will get access to some of your account data, in respect to the terms and conditions of these platforms. We also may collect certain information such as the ‘Like’ features.

### Purposes of processing and legal basis

The principal purpose of collecting your personal data is to offer you a safe, optimum, efficient and personalised experience. To this end, you agree and accept that we may use your personal data to:

  * provide our services and facilitate performance, including verifications relating to you;
  * resolve any problems so as to improve the use of our site and services;
  * personalise, assess, and improve our services, content and materials;
  * analyse the volume and history of your use of our services;
  * inform you about our services as well as our partners’ services and/or promotional offers;

We use the personal data submitted to us only in accordance with the applicable data protection legislation. For our clients who have signed up on our website, we processes your personal data for the performance of the contract between us to provide our services.

For our newsletter, use case studies and marketing material sign ups, we process your personal data based on the express consent you provide for this specific purpose.

### Third party disclosures

Personal data relating to you collected on our website are destined for GlobalExam’s own use and may be forwarded to GlobalExam’s partner companies so that we may obtain assistance and support in the context of carrying out our services. GlobalExam ensures that it has in place clear data protection requirements for all of its third party providers.

GlobalExam does not sell or rent your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes whatsoever.

In addition, GlobalExam does not disclose your personal data to third parties, except if: (1) you (or your account administrator acting on your behalf) requests or authorises disclosure thereof; (2) the disclosure is required to process transactions or supply services which you have requested (i.e. to check you are employing best practice in your mailings or for the purposes of processing an acquisition card with credit-card issuing companies); (3) GlobalExam is compelled to do so by a government authority or a regulatory body, in the case of a court order, a summons to appear in court or any other similar requisition from a government or the judiciary, or to establish or defend a legal application; or, (4) the third party is a subcontractor or sub-processor of GlobalExam in the carrying out of services (for example: GlobalExam uses the services of an Internet provider or a telecommunications company).

### Your data protection rights

In accordance with the French Data Protection Laws and the European General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR) you have a right of access, correction and removal of your personal data which you may exercise by sending us a support ticket.Your requests will be processed within 30 days. We may require that your request be accompanied by a photocopy of proof of identity or authority.

You are also able at any time to modify personal data by logging into your account and clicking on “edit my profile”.

### Cookies/Tracking

As a general rule, GlobalExam uses cookies and tracking to improve and personalise its Website and/or measure its audience. Cookies are files saved on your computer’s hard drive when browsing on the Internet and in particular on our site. A cookie is not used to gather your personal data without your knowledge but instead to record information on site browsing which can be read directly by GlobalExam on your subsequent visits and searches on the site.

You can choose to decline acceptance of all cookies, but your ability to browse certain pages of the site may be reduced. The cookies used by GlobalExam are intended to enable or facilitate communication, to enable the services requested by users to be supplied, to recognise users when they re-visit the site, to secure payments which users may make, to register the language spoken by users or other preferences necessary for the service requested to be supplied.

GlobalExam also uses analytics and tracking tools to measure website and digital data to gain customer insights, to carry out analyses on browsing experience so as to improve content, and to send targeted advertisements.

By default, cookies are not installed automatically (with the exception of those cookies needed to run the site and GlobalExam’s services, and you are informed of their installation by a banner). In accordance with the regulations that apply, GlobalExam will require your authorisation before implanting any other kind of cookie on your hard drive. To avoid being bothered by these routine requests for authorisation and to enjoy uninterrupted browsing, you can configure your computer to accept GlobalExam cookies or we are able to remember your refusal or acceptance of certain cookies. By default, browsers accept all cookies.

When you access third party sites directing you to our website, or when you are reading integration or social media links, cookies can be created by the companies disseminating these links. These third parties may be able to use cookies in the context of GlobalExam’s services (partners or other third parties supplying content or services available on the GlobalExam site) and are responsible for the cookies they install and it is their conditions on cookies which apply. GlobalExam assumes no liability in regard to the possible use of cookies by third parties. For more information, you are advised to check the cookie policy directly on these third party sites with regard to their use of cookies.

## Data Retention Periods

GlobalExam collects your personal data for the requirements of carrying out its contractual obligations as well as information about how and when you use our services and we retain this data in active databases, log files or other types of files so long as you use our services.

GlobalExam only stores your data for the time needed to provide to you our services, and your data will be deleted after closing your account (unless otherwise required by law). You are able to access your personal data for as long as you hold an active account with us.

## Location of Data Storage and Transfers

The host servers on which GlobalExam processes and stores its databases are located exclusively within the European Union.

GlobalExam will inform you immediately, to the extent we are legally authorised to do so, in case of any application or order originating from an administrative or judicial authority relating to your personal data.

## Security

Within the framework of its services, GlobalExam attributes the very highest importance to the security and integrity of its customers’ personal data.

Thus and in accordance with the GDPR, GlobalExam undertakes to take all pertinent precautions in order to preserve the security of the data and, in particular, to protect them against any accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, corruption, unauthorised circulation or access, as well as against any other form of unlawful processing or disclosure to unauthorised persons.

To this end, GlobalExam implements industry standard security measures to protect personal data from unauthorised disclosure. In using industry recommended methods of encoding, GlobalExam takes the measures necessary to protect information connected with payments and credit cards.

Moreover, in order to avoid in particular all unauthorised access, to guarantee accuracy and the proper use of the data, GlobalExam has put the appropriate electronic, physical and managerial procedures in place with a view to safeguarding and preserving the data gathered through its services.

Notwithstanding this, there is no absolute safety from piracy or hackers. That is why in the event a breach of security were to affect you, GlobalExam undertakes to inform you thereof without undue delay and to use its best efforts to take all possible measures to neutralise the intrusion and minimise the impacts. Should you suffer any loss by reason of the exploitation by a third party of a security breach, GlobalExam undertakes to provide you with every assistance necessary so you are able to assert your rights.

You should keep in mind that any user, customer or hacker who discovers and takes advantage of a breach in security renders him or herself liable to criminal prosecution and that GlobalExam will take all measures, including filing a complaint and/or bringing court action, to preserve the data and the rights of its users and of itself and to limit the impacts.

## Privacy Policy Changes

GlobalExam reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time, in particular pursuant to any changes made to the laws and regulations in force. We would recommend that you check these rules from time to time to stay informed of our procedures and rules relating to your personal information.
